wlfi.com 2016-12-06

# Privacy Policy | wlfi.com

**Media General, Inc.**  
**Effective Date** : February 18, 2016  
**Related** : Terms of Use

Media General, Inc., together with its Affiliates (collectively, “we,” “us,” or “our”), offers this website (the “Site”) and all related mobile or desktop applications (the “Applications,” and, together with the Site, the “Properties”), including without limitation all content, materials, information, software, products and services available on the Properties, to you, the user, conditioned upon your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy sets forth our online information collection practices. Specifically, it outlines the types of information that we gather from and about you while you are using the Properties and the ways in which we use and share this information. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information you may provide to us or that we may collect offline or through other means (for example, at a live event, via telephone, or through the mail).

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting or using the Site or the Applications, you agree to and accept the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, which are incorporated herein by reference. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you must immediately discontinue your use of the Properties.

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will post the changes on the Properties and update the Effective Date to reflect the date of the changes. You should periodically review this page to ensure that you understand the terms of the Privacy Policy currently in effect. Your use of the Properties after we post any such changes constitutes your acceptance of the modified terms of the Privacy Policy.

#### HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION

We may collect and store certain information about you that you voluntarily submit to us when you use the Properties. For example, we may collect information about you when you contact us using forms available through the Properties, sign up to receive communications from us, post information or content in publicly-accessible areas of the Properties, or enter a contest available through the Properties. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, information that can be used to identify or locate you, including without limitation your name, phone number, mailing address, email address, and geolocation data, is called “Personal Information.” Personal Information does not include de-identified or anonymized statistical or aggregated data about users or any information that you post in publicly-accessible areas of the Properties (such as message boards, blogs, or chat rooms) or otherwise publicly disclose on the Properties. Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily make any information available in publicly-accessible areas of the Properties, the content that you post can be seen, collected and used by other third parties. You acknowledge and agree that we are not responsible for any third-party use of such information.

We may also automatically collect and store certain information as you navigate the Properties. When you use the Site, we may use a standard feature found in browser software called “cookies.” Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. If you object to the use of cookies, please consult your browser’s documentation for instructions on how to disable or delete them or contact us at [privacypolicy@mediageneral.com](mailto:privacypolicy@mediageneral.com). You should be advised, however, that cookies are required for certain functions of the Properties and if you disable or delete them, you may not be able to access or use certain functions.

The Properties also may use web beacons (single-pixel graphic files also known as “clear GIFs”) to recognize users, access cookies, or to count users who visit the Properties or open HTML-formatted email messages. You may stop the use of some web beacons by turning off your browser’s cookies.

When you use the Applications, we may use Identifiers for Advertisers (IFA) or Google Advertising Identifiers (AID) to collect information about your device and location and to serve advertisements to you. For example, we may collect information about the type of device you use to access the Applications (including without limitation the device make, model, manufacturer, operating system/platform, and language) as well as your location when you use the device. If you object to this practice, please consult your device’s documentation for information on how to disable collection of IFA and AID information.

#### HOW WE USE AND SHARE INFORMATION

We use the Personal Information and other information we collect from and about you while you are using the Properties in a variety of ways, including without limitation to:

  * Perform normal business operations such as billing, collecting and accounting;
  * Process and deliver products and services that you request;
  * Respond to communications from you;
  * Collect information about your computer’s connection to the Internet;
  * Improve the Properties and the delivery of the Properties to you;
  * Measure traffic to the Properties and estimate the number of unique users of our Properties;
  * Track user trends and patterns;
  * Personalize the Properties for you, customize features that appear on the Properties, and serve advertisements to you;
  * Assist with fraud detection efforts and debugging;
  * Identify the type of device you use and its capabilities or your location;
  * Prevent you from having to re-enter your preferences on certain areas of the Properties where you may have entered preference information before;
  * Contact you regarding the Properties, products or services offered through the Properties, or special offers, contests or promotions; and
  * Track and collect general usage information regarding users of the Properties.

We may provide information about you, including without limitation Personal Information, to third parties such as service providers, contractors, and advertisers, for a variety of purposes, including online behavioral advertising or multi-site advertising. We reserve the right to use, and to disclose to others, all information (including without limitation your Personal Information) collected from and about you while you are using the Properties in any way and for any purpose, including without limitation to enable us or a third party to provide you with information about products and services. We reserve the right to release any information in our possession, including without limitation Personal Information, when such release is necessary or appropriate to comply with law or legal process, to protect the rights, property or safety of users of the Properties or the public, or when we otherwise believe, in our sole discretion, that such release is appropriate.

Please also note that as our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the event that we sell some or all of our assets, or one or more of our Properties are acquired by another company, information about our users may be among the transferred assets. In the event of such a transfer, we cannot guarantee that this Privacy Policy will continue to govern your information.

We do not generally keep email correspondence, except for those emails that relate to our on-air programs or operations. As required by the Federal Communications Commission (“FCC”), if any part of your email correspondence relates to station programming or operations, we must place such correspondence in the station’s FCC Public Inspection File. Therefore, you acknowledge and agree that any Personal Information contained in certain emails, including Personal Information knowingly received from a child under the age of thirteen, may be disclosed to the general public. We therefore caution you that you should not put any confidential Personal Information in any email correspondence to us that pertains to station programming or operations. You understand and agree that we are not responsible for Personal Information that is disclosed in emails that are made available to the general public in compliance with FCC regulations.

#### COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION BY THIRD PARTIES

We may use third parties to help us administer and operate the Properties and to provide us with internal support. For example, we may use third parties to help us with calendaring events on the Properties and administering contests on the Properties (the “Third Party Partners”). We may share your Personal Information and other information about you with our Third Party Partners in our sole discretion. To the extent the Third Party Partners place advertisements, links, cookies, or other technologies on our Properties, however, these items are not under our control and they are governed by the privacy policies and terms of use of our Third Party Partners. If you have questions about the practices or policies of our Third Party Partners, you should visit that party’s website and review its policies.

Some of our third-party advertisers and ad servers that place and present advertising on the Properties also may collect information from you via cookies, web beacons or similar technologies. These third-party advertisers and ad servers may use the information they collect to help present their advertisements, to help measure and research the advertisements’ effectiveness, or for other purposes. The use and collection of your information by these third-party advertisers and ad servers is governed by the relevant third-party’s privacy policy and is not covered by our Privacy Policy. If you have any concerns about a third party’s use of cookies or web beacons or use of your information, you should visit that party’s website and review its privacy policy.

Third-party ad providers who display advertisements on our Properties may choose to utilize the Ad Choices icon. You can click on the icon to exercise certain choices with respect to interest-based advertising. To learn more about exercising choice with respect to interest-based advertising, you may also visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>.

#### THIRD-PARTY LINKS AND PLATFORMS

The Properties may include links to other web sites not owned or operated by us. Links to third-party websites do not indicate our endorsement or sponsorship of the information, products, or services available on such websites. When you access another website, you become subject to the privacy policy and terms of use governing that website. You should therefore carefully review the privacy policy and terms of use governing any such third-party website.

You may be able to use certain social media platforms (e.g., Twitter) via our Properties. Any such social media platform’s terms of use and privacy policies may also govern your activity when you partake in this activity. We recommend that you familiarize yourself with the rules governing a social media platform before using it via our Properties.

#### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

The Properties are not directed to children under the age of thirteen and we do not knowingly collect through the Properties personal information, as defined by the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, from children under the age of thirteen. Children under the age of thirteen are not allowed to submit any personal information to us, enter any contests, sweepstakes, or promotions made available through the Properties, or post in any publicly-viewable area of the Properties (e.g., message boards, chat rooms, etc.). If we become aware that we have received personal information from a user under the age of thirteen, we will delete such personal information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personal information from children under the age of thirteen.

The provisions of this Privacy Policy relating to the collection and retention of personal information from a child under the age of thirteen do not apply where such information was submitted as correspondence relating to station programming and operations.

#### HOW TO VIEW, MODIFY OR DELETE YOUR INFORMATION

If you have subscribed to our email newsletters, you may unsubscribe by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email that you receive from us. Otherwise, if you wish to change your subscriber information, modify your subscriptions, or view, modify, or delete any Personal Information that you have submitted to us, please contact us at [privacypolicy@mediageneral.com](mailto:privacypolicy@mediageneral.com). Please be advised that you are responsible for notifying us in the event your mobile phone number changes or is deactivated.

#### INFORMATION RETENTION

Unless you contact us to request the deletion of your Personal Information, we will retain such information for as long as it is necessary to fulfill a legitimate business purpose or as required by law.

#### SECURITY

We employ certain physical, administrative, and technical measures in an attempt to protect your Personal Information. Although we do attempt to keep your Personal Information secure, we cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Information. You use the Properties at your own risk and your communications with us are subject to all of the risks associated with the Internet, including without limitation unauthorized access and use.

#### QUESTIONS REGARDING PRIVACY

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, our privacy practices, or your dealings with us, you may contact us at [privacypolicy@mediageneral.com](mailto:privacypolicy@mediageneral.com).
